what's up guys turb hook today I'm doing
a product review today on Guru tobacco's
new hookah refresh Flavor now this is a
product that claims to make your uh
hooka bowl last three times as longer as
well as get rid of any harshest you
might have and gu tobacco is nice enough
to send me five samples of different
flavors to try and I'm going to give you
my honest opinion about its H
performance so um yeah a little bit
about this product it comes in a nice
little tiny uh um dispenser with a
generous amount of juice which I'm
assuming is a mix of Glycerin and
flavoring and little needle end that it
comes out with to poke through the
actual holes of your foil and drop in
the flavoring so um yeah uh they're nice
send me five different flavors of uh
orange petal watermelon no flavor which
you could actually just put in a regular
bowl and it just uh makes it less harsh
without changing the flavor um Misty
mint and lime so um right now I'm
actually I actually uh loaded the bowl
of Starbuzz an hour and a half ago um uh
it was dying out around an hour and a
half or so and I put more coals on it to
actually get a little bit harsh so um
right now I actually just took off the
coals and put seven drops of orange
petal into it and uh three more coals on
there so let's see how the cloud out put
is as you guys can see amazing white
clouds I would actually honestly say
that this uh actually improves the cloud
performance too uh these are actually
thicker clouds I actually was getting
with starb I would say uh this past bow
session I had but um yeah uh it imately
got rid of all the harshness that I had
uh about a couple minutes ago but yeah
so this is definitely a revolution
flaver that I love um the product the
only thing that I uh kind of would
recommend for them to change a product
is the performance of these uh uh the
containers themselves um it was a little
difficult to p like when you put the
bowl on and it's hot and it's done it's
kind of hard to take off the bowl when
it's hot so uh when you put it
vertically the actual weight of the all
the juice kind of makes it drip out and
that kind of gets on top of your foil
and uh when you put the coals in there
it makes a little mess and it kind of
smells but it's nothing too bad but uh
it just leaks a little bit so I mean
that's easily fixable by just taking the
bowl off and then tilting it and then
putting in so uh that's not really a
problem but maybe they could change
something a little bit like that I would
like but um yeah of the flavor
performance I mean I'm just getting
amazing like orange petal just uh I was
smoking uh watermelon freeze and it was
dyed out and I put this and now just
straight up chaste the orange petal
delicious flavor but um I would also say
there's different uh different flavor
strengths with different flavors like
such as my favorites are orange petal uh
lime and Misty mint just because they
give out amazing just like Flavor really
powerful
flavor excuse me but um yeah I've
actually used all these before and
during the bowls uh Bowl sessions and uh
I personally like actually using it uh
after or during because um what I've
noticed actually mixing before it
definitely adds a new flavor and mix
however it gets a little uh it makes the
flavor a little bit more subtle but you
don't notice that all when you actually
put that at the end of the bowl it
actually revives and just like makes the
flavor way more powerful but um yeah for
the whole product review I mean it
definitely gets rid of any harshness it
definitely lasts uh makes the bull last
way longer too um I've actually had one
of these last from a range of 2 and 1
half hours to three and a half hours of
friends so I mean it definitely uh
satisfies the claims that it does make
it last three times longer as well as uh
get rid of any harshness so this product
does exactly what it does um and I'm
just like really happy with it so um
yeah out of a product review i' rate
this about 94 out of 100 the only place
that loses points is uh like I said the
the performance of these the little tiny
needles I mean the needles are small
enough where it can go in the holes and
that's amazing I love that but um like I
said if you tilt it back like this like
straight up it'll start leaking a little
bit it's a little difficult to get into
the bowl and uh maybe just like I'm not
sure if it's just a watermelon or just
the other flavor but like you can't
really taste uh I mean you could really
taste it but um it makes the flavor more
subtle if you do it before the bowl
instead of during the bowl but um this
is a great review or sorry this is a
great product overall and I definitely
enjoy it so thanks for you guys for
watching definitely try this out if
you're interested so uh thanks guys